Finding Aid for the Alice Parr Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Alice Parr Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0609
.42 linear_feet
Biography/History
Alice Parr, of Dyersburg Tennessee, received a Bachelor degree from George Peabody College in 1901. She later taught in the Dyersburg School System.
Scope and Contents
This .21 linear feet collection is comprised of 22 photographs, in 13 file folders, taken between 1899 and 1902 of Alice Parr, her classmates, and a University of Nashville school building. The photographs are in alphabetical order where identified, otherwise grouped by date.
- Photographs
  - Abbott, Father (1), 1900 (Folder 1.)
  - Carley, H. T. – (2), 1901, 1902 (Folder 2.)
  - Garrett, Dr. (2), 1900 (Folder 3.)
  - Lampton, Professor (1), 1899 (Folder 4.)
  - Newell, Hattie Lou (1), n.d. (Folder 5.)
  - Parr, Alice (1), 1901 (Folder 6.)
  - Parr, Alice and Em (1) (Folder 7.)
  - Schumpert, B. T. (1), n.d. (Folder 8.)
  - White, Lou (1), 1902 (Folder 9.)
  - Unidentified Photographs (5), 1900 (Folder 10.)
  - Unidentified Photographs (3), 1901 (Folder 11.)
  - Unidentified Photographs (2), n.d. (Folder 12.)
  - University of Nashville (1), n.d. (Folder 13.)